{
    "subject": "resource/Todd_McCaffrey",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Todd J. McCaffrey (born 27 April 1956 as Todd Johnson) is an Irish American author of science fiction best known for continuing the Dragonriders of Pern series in collaboration with his mother Anne McCaffrey.",
    "human_readable": "Todd McCaffrey's abstract is Todd J. McCaffrey (born 27 April 1956 as Todd Johnson) is an Irish American author of science fiction best known for continuing the Dragonriders of Pern series in collaboration with his mother Anne McCaffrey.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9749414920806885,
            "question": "With whom did Todd J. McCaffrey collaborate on the Dragonriders of Pern series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9371896386146545,
            "question": "When was Todd J. McCaffrey born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9371197819709778,
            "question": "Is Todd J. McCaffrey an American author?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9323587417602539,
            "question": "What series of books is Todd J. McCaffrey best known for continuing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9217382669448853,
            "question": "What is the name of Todd J. McCaffrey's mother?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9060683250427246,
            "question": "What is Todd J. McCaffrey's birth name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8458197116851807,
            "question": "What nationality is Todd J. McCaffrey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8106863498687744,
            "question": "Who is the author of the original Dragonriders of Pern series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7852540016174316,
            "question": "What genre does Todd J. McCaffrey write in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7563297748565674,
            "question": "What type of work does Todd J. McCaffrey create?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Todd McCaffrey's abstract is Todd J. McCaffrey (born 27 April 1956 as Todd Johnson) is an Irish American author of science fiction best known for continuing the Dragonriders of Pern series in collaboration with his mother Anne McCaffrey.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5451_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre does Todd J. McCaffrey write in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5451_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is the author of the original Dragonriders of Pern series?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5451_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Todd J. McCaffrey?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5451_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5451_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5451_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5451_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5451_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5451_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5451_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5451_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5451_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5451_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5451_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can answer your question:\n\nResponse:\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents contain information that supports the statement about Todd McCaffrey's name, nationality, profession, and his work on the Dragonriders of Pern series. Specifically, they mention:\n\n- His full name is Todd J. McCaffrey but he was born as Todd Johnson.\n- He is an Irish American author of science fiction.\n- He is known for continuing the Dragonriders of Pern series in collaboration with his mother Anne McCaffrey.\n\nTherefore, the given abstract accurately reflects information found in the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}